ninjamock.com 2018-12-25

# We respect the privacy of NinjaMock community

  1. ## Agreement and Parties

NinjaMock Inc. ("NinjaMock," "us," or "we") respects the privacy and personal information of the members of the NinjaMock community. This privacy policy applies to information we receive when you use the NinjaMock website or NinjaMock software (collectively, the "NinjaMock Service" or "Service"). This privacy policy ("privacy policy" or "policy") is an agreement between NinjaMock and you, as the user of the NinjaMock Service ("you"). This agreement tells you when this policy is effective, how we may change this policy, what information we collect from you, how we might use that information, how you can review or change the personal information you provided to us, and the steps we take to ensure that your personal information is protected. We share your personal information only with your consent or as described in this policy.

Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about how NinjaMock treats personally identifiable information. We follow principles that are supported by the Danish Trade Commission. If you have comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the email and/or mailing address provided at the end of this policy.

  2. ## Agreement to Terms of Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

Any NinjaMock Service you wish to use is purely voluntary. You are not required to provide any personal information to us unless you choose to access features of the Service which require such information. If you do not agree with the terms of this policy or NinjaMock's Terms of Use related to the NinjaMock Service, then please do not provide us with personal information, exit this website immediately, and discontinue using the site or any component of the Service. NinjaMock's Terms of Use, and your end user license agreement related to any software provided by NinjaMock that you download and install, are expressly incorporated into this policy by reference and made a part of this policy. By using the NinjaMock Service, you signify that you agree to the terms of this privacy policy as well as to our Terms of Use.

  3. ## Effective Date of And Changes To Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is effective as of July 6th 2016, and will remain in effect except with respect to any of its provisions that are changed in the future, in which case the changes will become effective thirty (30) days after they are posted to the website or we otherwise notify you of the changes. Use of information we collect is subject to the policy in effect at the time such information was collected. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time and you should check this privacy policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified policy and your agreement to abide and be bound by the modified policy. We will also revise the "last updated" date found at the beginning of this privacy policy when we post changes to it.

  4. ## Policy Applicable to Online Activities Only

The privacy policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the internet, and therefore beyond NinjaMock's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. This privacy policy only applies to information collected through the NinjaMock Service and otherwise as described in this policy.

  5. ## Personal Information About You

    1. ### Types of Information Collected

We may ask you for certain information, referred to as "personal information", which includes information that pertains to your identity. Such information may include, but is not limited to, information such as your name, email address, and credit card information.

    2. ### Personal Information You Provide to Us

You may be required to provide personal information to access or use certain parts or features of the NinjaMock Service. For example, you will be asked to provide your name and a valid email address to establish an account at http://ninjamock.com. If you wish to establish a paid NinjaMock account, you will also be asked to provide credit card account and billing information. If you do not provide the requested personal information, you may not be able to access or use the particular component of the Service where such information is required.

    3. ### Survey Information

From time to time, NinjaMock may ask its registered users to participate in surveys. These surveys are purely optional and help us improve the NinjaMock Service and provide aggregate information which we think may interest our registered users and visitors. We may use the information that you voluntarily provide as part of your survey response in the manner outlined in this Privacy Policy. In addition, if you choose to participate in a NinjaMock survey, any information you provide to us, including personal information, will be linked with your account in our system and to any personal information contained therein. We may also use the information you provide in the aggregate to help us generate statistics regarding use of the NinjaMock Service. For example, if you reveal in a survey response that you are a professor, NinjaMock will know that you are a professor, will retain that information in association with your registered user account, and may publish aggregate statistics based thereon (for example, statistics regarding what portion of our educational users are professors versus what portion of our educational users are students). If you would not like your information to be used in this way, please do not participate in NinjaMock surveys or, if participating, please provide us only with information you consent to our use of in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

  6. ## Personal Information You Provide About Others

Some components of the NinjaMock Service allow you to share content and personal messages you upload with others by generating messages directly to those other individuals. To use this feature, we require you provide us with a valid email address for each recipient. NinjaMock uses these email addresses only to share your content and personal messages (at your direction). We use this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, and do not store it after this one-time email is sent. This one-time email may also contain a short description and explanation of the NinjaMock Service.

  7. ## General Information We May Collect

    1. ### Types of Information Collected

There may be other instances in which we collect information from you that is more general in nature ("general information"). Such information may include information recorded by our server logs from your browser such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address (which enables us to identify your computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (TCP/IP) network like the internet), and the specific web page you requested. Such general information, including the clickstream data and cookies, as mentioned below, may be collected from you whenever you access or use the NinjaMock Service, whether or not you provide us with any other personal information.

    2. ### Clickstream Data

When you use the NinjaMock Service we may collect "clickstream data" (server address, domain name, etc.). This information can be combined with information you have provided to us, which will enable us to analyze and better customize your visits. We may use clickstream data for traffic analysis or e-commerce analysis of our services, to determine which features within the NinjaMock Service are most or least effective or useful to you.

    3. ### Cookies

A cookie is a small string of information that the website you visit transfers to your computer for identification purposes. Cookies can be used to follow your activity throughout the NinjaMock Service and that information helps us to understand your preferences and improve your experience. For a detailed description of the types of cookies we use and on how you can control the use of cookies, please see our Cookie Policy.

  8. ## Use and Sharing of Information

    1. ### To Provide Products and Services to You

We will use the personal information you provide and any general information we receive from you to provide NinjaMock products and services to you, which include the following:

      1. To process orders you may place at [www.ninjamock.com](http://www.ninjamock.com/).
      2. To assist those who help us in designing and operating the NinjaMock Service or help us analyze collected data. These parties will only use your data for the purpose of carrying out the work as agreed with us and will be required to keep the information confidential.
      3. To send you information or materials via email about products, offers, and news we think might interest you. This information may relate to products, offers, and news of NinjaMock or its licensees or selected commercial partners. (If you no longer wish to receive any emails from us, or if you want to modify your personal data or want your personal data to be deleted from our database, please see "canceling your account, opting out email and modifying personal information" below.)
      4. To share your Public User Content with other NinjaMock users who we think might be interested, including with other users from your organization. In addition to your Public User Content we may also share the username associated with your public, paid or educational account with other users registered with an e-mail address using the domain of the same organization as your e-mail address. If you are not a habitual resident of a Member State of the European Economic Area, we may also share your name and your email address with the organization having the same domain as your email address.
      5. To facilitate collaboration between users as set out in point 6.1 of our Terms of Use.
      6. To analyze visits to the NinjaMock website and learn about the interests of our visitors in the aggregate and also on a personal level to better understand your interests and needs, so we can improve our products and services and deliver to you the type of content, features, and promotions that you are most interested in.
      7. To publish aggregate statistics regarding our user base. For example, we may choose to publish statistics regarding how many registered NinjaMock users live in the U.S. versus how many live in Europe. If you complete a NinjaMock survey that asks for employment information, we may publish statistics regarding which professions are most likely to use or not use NinjaMock.
    2. ### Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if NinjaMock or substantially all of its assets were acquired, customer information would likely be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of NinjaMock may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

    3. ### Protection of NinjaMock and Others

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law, enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of NinjaMock, our employees, our customers, or others. We may disclose personal or general information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, which may include responding to requests and court orders from jurisdictions outside the State of Denmark. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful, as determined in our sole discretion.

    4. ### With Your Consent

Except as set forth herein, we will notify you or obtain your consent before your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. Registered users may, at any time, select to stop receiving emails from us by unsubscribing an email.

    5. ### Retention of Your Information

We will only retain your information to the extent: (a) it is needed for the purposes which we have conveyed to you; (b) we are required by law to maintain such information; or (c) it is needed for us to address any issues or inquiries that you may have. When your information is no longer required, we will dispose of such information by destroying it or erasing it.

  9. ## Protection Of Your Information

    1. ### Security Measures

In order to protect both the personal information and the general information that we receive from you through your use of the NinjaMock Service, we have implemented various security measures. For example, when you enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number) on our online forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We also follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

    2. ### Risk of Interception

Please keep in mind, however, that whenever you give out personal information online there is a risk that third parties may intercept and use that information. While NinjaMock strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. By using the NinjaMock Service, you expressly acknowledge and agree that we do not guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through your use of the NinjaMock Service and that any personal information, general information, or other data or information received from you through your use of the NinjaMock Service is provided to us at your own risk, which you expressly assume.

  10. ## No Use Of This Service By Minors Permitted

    1. ### Registration Declined for Minors

The NinjaMock Service is intended only for those who are at least 13 years old. Personal registration information submitted by a minor violates the website terms of use and will not be accepted. Any general information provided by minor and gathered (for example, through the use of cookies) during his or her visit may be used as indicated in this privacy policy. NinjaMock is committed to protecting the privacy of children and has no intention of collecting personal data from minors. We encourage parents and guardians of minors to regularly check and monitor their children's use of email and other activities online.

    2. ### Notice Concerning Children

PLEASE NOTE: The NinjaMock Service is general audience service, and does not direct any of its content, products, or services specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children's privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a user of the NinjaMock Service is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user's account. If you have such information, please contact us at [ninjas@ninjamock.com](mailto:ninjas@ninjamock.com).

  11. ## Links to Third Parties

For your convenience and to improve the usage of the NinjaMock Service we may insert links to third party websites. This privacy policy does not apply to such third party websites. These links take you outside our Service, and off the NinjaMock site, and are beyond our control. This includes links from partners that may use NinjaMock's logos as part of a co-branding agreement. The sites those links can take you to have their own separate privacy policy and although we seek to protect the integrity of our Service, NinjaMock is not liable for the content and activities of those sites. Your visits and access to such websites is at your own risk. Please note that those other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.

  12. ## Canceling Your Account, Opting Out of Email, and Modifying Personal Information

You may cancel your account and you may unsubscribe any emails from NinjaMock at any time. You may cancel your account, opt out of, or modify your personal information, by logging in and visiting your **My Account** page and following the instructions provided. We encourage you promptly to update your personal information when it changes. Information concerning your past behavior with the Service may be retained by NinjaMock as long as necessary for the purposes set out above.

Please note that although you may opt out of receiving certain emails, NinjaMock reserves the right to communicate with you via email regarding specific products and services you have ordered, requested, inquired about or information that is fundamental to the service.

  13. ## Questions or Comments

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns relating to the NinjaMock Service or this privacy policy, please send an email to [ninjas@ninjamock.com](mailto:ninjas@ninjamock.com) or write to us at:

You may contact us by visiting: [www.ninjamock.com](http://www.ninjamock.com/)

You can mail us at: [ninjas@ninjamock.com](mailto:ninjas@ninjamock.com)

NinjaMock's mailing address is:

NinjaMock  
Margrethevej 4,1.  
2900 Hellerup  
Denmark

We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
